http://www.musicbox-online.com/privacy.html

Privacy Policy for The Music Box
The Music Box and Musicbox-Online.com fully respects your right to privacy.
The Music Box
will never sell, rent, or share your personal information with anyone without your permission.
Any personal information that you provide to us will remain private
unless otherwise indicated.
For further details, please read this statement thoroughly and carefully.
Personal information can include but is not limited your name, street address, e-mail address, billing information,
phone number, date of birth, click-through activity, and other similar items that you provide to us.
The Music Box and Musicbox-Online reserves the right to update this policy at any time.
Traffic Data
Like every other website, The Music Box and Musicbox-Online.com collects basic traffic data for
all visitors to our site.
This information can include the visitor's IP address, domain name, referral data, and browser and platform type.
From time to time, the traffic information we collect is aggregated and then shared with
publicity firms, record labels, and other similar entities.
However, except in
cases involving civil or criminal litigation, including but not limited to
defense of our copyrights, we will never share any information that is personal or identifiable.
No one
will ever be able to identify you or contact you based upon the data that we provide.
The Music Box and Musicbox-Online.com makes use of Google's Analytics program to aggregate and track data.
The Google Analytics program
does place a cookie on user's machines that allows it to collect anonymous traffic data.
Google maintains its own privacy policy.
The Music Box and Musicbox-Online.com also is a member of the LinkShare Network.
LinkShare may make use of cookies and other methods to track your internet usage.
Contests, Giveaways, and Other Promotional Ventures
The Music Box and Musicbox-Online.com hosts its own contests.
In order to expedite the selection and processing of winners of these
contests, we will collect personal information at the time of entry.
On occasion, we are asked to share the personal information that we collect for a specific contest with its sponsor.
This
can include but is not limited to your name, address, billing address, e-mail address, phone number, date of birth, and other similar items.
We always will make it clear to you at the time of entry when we are asked to share this information, and we always will ask for your permission to share your
personal information.
We will never make it a requirement for you to share your information in order to enter our contests.
E-Mail List
The Music Box and Musicbox-Online.com e-mail list is maintained using Yahoo's Group E-mail System.
The Music Box and
Musicbox-Online.com will do everything within our power to protect the integrity of our compiled list of e-mail addresses, and we will never share this information with a third-party without your
express written consent.
Yahoo and AT&T, which operates the platform, has its own privacy policy.
Other Sites
To enhance your user experience, The Music Box and Musicbox-Online.com provides, from time to time, links to other websites.
We cannot control
and are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other websites.
If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policy, please let us know!
Copyright ©
1994-2014
The Music Box
Artists: A  B  C  D  E  F  G  H  I  J  K  L  M  N  O  P  Q  R  S  T  U  V  W  X  Y  Z__________________BOOKS  MOVIES  FAMILY MUSIC  HOLIDAY MUSIC  COMPILATIONS__________________Library of Congress/National Serials Data Program: ISSN 1941-224XAbout Us  Contact Us  Privacy  User Agreement  CharitiesNO PORTION OF THIS SITE MAY BE REPRODUCED WITHOUT PERMISSION
